100 days. Why is 100 days significant?
>> The milestone is no alcohol for 100
days.
>> [__] A, man. Congratulations. That is
huge.
>> It is huge.
>> What made the difference this time
around?
>> I think that initially it was fear of
death, which was largely driven by my
doctor calling me up and saying, "Your
liver enzymes are like whatever it was,
5x, 7x what they should be."
>> Oh, wow. Okay.
>> The nice thing obviously about the liver
is that until you're at that point of no
return, it's pretty damn good at healing
itself. And my liver enzymes snap back
to normal ranges within 4 weeks, which
is great to see.
>> What would you say made the difference
this time around? You had the health
scare, or at least the doctor saying,
"Hey, hotshot."
>> It was surrounding myself with people
that had done this before. I know right
now three people that have successfully
done 12-step programs. I knew that there
were people that, and I'd seen this,
that had stuck to it with the help and
support of these people, and they gather
around you and really give you a kind of
a toolkit to lean into. And for me, that
has been really understanding that it's
not about the 3 months. It's just about
winning today. And so, if you can
reframe it as just not today, yeah, I
can have a drink tomorrow, but just not
today.
>> Not today, Satan. Not today, Satan.